<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- Gizmo -->
	<TransformLabel>Transform</TransformLabel>
	<LightCopyLabel>Copy {0}</LightCopyLabel>
	<LightCopyDescription>Create a light copy from the photo of: {0}. The light copy will vanish once it is no longer used.</LightCopyDescription>
	<LightCopyPhotoClearLabel>Delete photos</LightCopyPhotoClearLabel>
	<LightCopyPhotoClearDescription>Delete all currently saved photos</LightCopyPhotoClearDescription>
	<LightCopyPhotoClearDisabled>No photos</LightCopyPhotoClearDisabled>
	<InjectDustLabel>Inject {0}</InjectDustLabel>
	<InjectDustDescription>Inject yourself with a {0} to strenghten your Aura. Your Aura will regenerate fast and you will deal additional melee damage according to the crystal's element. Causes alot of pain.</InjectDustDescription>
	<AbilityDescConsumeAura>Consume the stolen Aura: {0}. If you don't have an Aura, you will obtain the stolen Aura's full potential. Otherwise this will increase your Aura's strenght and certain abilities from the stolen Aura (which are not Aura specific) become available to you.</AbilityDescConsumeAura>

	<!-- Gizmo disabled reasons -->
	<DisabledNotEquipped>{0} is on the ground</DisabledNotEquipped>
	<DisabledNoAmmunition>{0} needed to use this ability</DisabledNoAmmunition>
	<DisabledNeedsItemEquipped>Cannot transform without {0} equipped</DisabledNeedsItemEquipped>
	<DisabledNotEnoughAura>{0} has not enough Aura to use this ability</DisabledNotEnoughAura>
	<DisabledNoDamageAbosrbed>{0} has no absorbed damage</DisabledNoDamageAbosrbed>
	<DisabledNoMeleeWeapon>{0} has no melee weapon equipped</DisabledNoMeleeWeapon>
	<DisabledNotInBoxForm>The camera is not in box form</DisabledNotInBoxForm>

	<!-- Mod Options -->
	<AuraEveryoneLabel>Every pawn has an Aura</AuraEveryoneLabel>
	<AuraEveryoneTooltip>Even pawns without the Aura or Semblance traits will have a small aura (default: disabled)</AuraEveryoneTooltip>
	<AuraLabel>Pawns can unlock their Aura</AuraLabel>
	<AuraTooltip>Pawns can unlock their Aura under certain circumstances (default: enabled)</AuraTooltip>
	<SemblanceLabel>Pawns can discover their Semblance</SemblanceLabel>
	<SemblanceTooltip>Pawns can discover their semblance through certain events or actions (default: enabled)</SemblanceTooltip>
	<EveryoneMakesPhotosForJoyLabel>Every pawn can make photos for joy</EveryoneMakesPhotosForJoyLabel>
	<EveryoneMakesPhotosForJoyTooltip>Every pawn with a camera can make photos for joy, even the ones without Semblance Velvet (default: disabled)</EveryoneMakesPhotosForJoyTooltip>
	<HideAuraWhenMultiselectLabel>Hide Aura when multiple Pawns are selected</HideAuraWhenMultiselectLabel>
	<HideAuraWhenMultiselectTooltip>Hide the Aura status and abilities if multiple pawns are selected (default: disabled)</HideAuraWhenMultiselectTooltip>
	<FixTraitDisabledWorkTagsLabel>Show disabled work tags in trait description</FixTraitDisabledWorkTagsLabel>
	<FixTraitDisabledWorkTagsTooltip>Show disabled work tags in trait descriptions, will also affect traits from other mods. (Vanilla Rimworld doesn't show them)</FixTraitDisabledWorkTagsTooltip>
	<EarliestNuckelaveeLabel>Earliest Nuckelavee appearance possible after days: (default 30)</EarliestNuckelaveeLabel>

	<!-- Aura Gizmo -->
	<AuraGizmoLabel>{0}'s Aura</AuraGizmoLabel>
	<AngerLevelNotAngryLabel>not angry</AngerLevelNotAngryLabel>
	<AngerLevelAnnoyedLabel>annoyed</AngerLevelAnnoyedLabel>
	<AngerLevelAngryLabel>angry</AngerLevelAngryLabel>
	<AngerLevelRagingLabel>raging</AngerLevelRagingLabel>
	<AngerLevelLostHairLabel>lost a hair kind of angry</AngerLevelLostHairLabel>
	<AdamAbsorbDamageLabel>absorbed damage</AdamAbsorbDamageLabel>
	<SemblanceAbilityCastNoAura>{PAWN_nameDef} has not enough Aura to cast this ability.</SemblanceAbilityCastNoAura>
	<SemblanceAuraCost>Aura cost</SemblanceAuraCost>
	<InjectCrystalLabel>Inject Dust Crysal</InjectCrystalLabel>
	<InjectCrystalDescription>Inject {0}, granting a buff in melee damage and an inporved Aura. Each Dust Crystal will grant a different buff that can stack up to 3 times. A 3 times stacked buff will wear of after 8 ingame hours. Injecting Dust Crystals will cause pain. The pain will increase the more Dust Crysals are injected.</InjectCrystalDescription>
	<InjectCrystalNoAmmo>There is no ammunition left in the Dust Crystal belt</InjectCrystalNoAmmo>
	<InjectCrystalDowned>{0} is downed</InjectCrystalDowned>

	<!-- Raven Portal Gizmo -->
	<RavenPortalDisabled>Another portal is still active</RavenPortalDisabled>
	<RavenPortalFloatMenuLabel>Go through portal</RavenPortalFloatMenuLabel>
	<RavenPortalBondLabel>Portal to {0}</RavenPortalBondLabel>
	<RavenPortalBondDescription>Create a portal to {0} that will last for 30 seconds.</RavenPortalBondDescription>
	<RavenBondOpinionLow>{0} does not like {1} enough to create a bond</RavenBondOpinionLow>
	
	<!-- Blake Shadow Clone Gizmo -->
	<BlakeUseDefaultCloneLabel>Default clone</BlakeUseDefaultCloneLabel>
	<BlakeUseDefaultCloneDescription>Use the default clone with no elemental capabilities</BlakeUseDefaultCloneDescription>
	<BlakeUseFireCloneLabel>Fire clone</BlakeUseFireCloneLabel>
	<BlakeUseFireCloneDescription>Use fire clones, that explode after 3 seconds, but do not hurt the creator of the clone. Each created clone will use one vial of powdered Fire Dust. If no powdered Dust belt ist equipped, or no vials remain, the default clone will be used instead.</BlakeUseFireCloneDescription>
	<BlakeUseIceCloneLabel>Ice clone</BlakeUseIceCloneLabel>
	<BlakeUseIceCloneDescription>Use ice clones, that freeze any melee attackers. Each created clone will use one vial of powdered Ice Dust. If no powdered Dust belt ist equipped, or no vials remain, the default clone will be used instead.</BlakeUseIceCloneDescription>
	<BlakeUseGravityCloneLabel>Stone clone</BlakeUseGravityCloneLabel>
	<BlakeUseGravityCloneDescription>Use stone clones, that grant alot of cover and have a long lifespan. Each created clone will use one vial of powdered Gravity Dust. If no powdered Dust belt ist equipped, or no vials remain, the default clone will be used instead.</BlakeUseGravityCloneDescription>

	<!-- Yang Retrun Damage -->
	<YangReturnDamageLabel>Return damage</YangReturnDamageLabel>
	<YangReturnDamageDescription>Toggle on to deal additional damage based on how many damage has been taken. Can be manually toggled off. Will automatically activate at 75 absorbed damage. The effect will wear off after 6 ingame hours.</YangReturnDamageDescription>

	<!-- Hazel Ignore Pain -->
	<HazelIgnorePainLabel>Ignore pain</HazelIgnorePainLabel>
	<HazelIgnorePainDescription>Toggle on to ignore pain. Can be manually toggled off. The effect will wear off after 6 ingame hours. Can be activated when downed, but be careful to not ignore the pawn's wounds, as the pawn can die while feeling no pain.</HazelIgnorePainDescription>

</LanguageData>